<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>Introduction Ah, the Realme 5 Pro. It's been what - five years? Three? Actually, it's been only one year and yet Realme is launching its fifth generation of smartphones. The maker has been trying to cater to users' every imaginable need and quite successfully at that. So, after the Realme X that brought us immersive AMOLED experience, let's meet the camera-centric Realme 5 Pro.    It might have been just over a year, but we are glad Realme has found its MO - catchy designs, breezy performance, and good camera skillset. And it's been delivering those on unbelievably low prices ever since. The Realme 5 Pro doesn't lose focus on what's important either - there is the signature dazzling looks, the upper-tier Snapdragon 712 chip, and company's first quad-camera setup.  Realme 5 Pro review Indeed, Realme has jumped from dual- straight to quad-camera arrangements. And the Realme 5 Pro setup is rather impressive with a 48MP primary, an 8MP ultrawide, a 2MP macro, and 2MP portrait snappers. Advanced 2x digital zoom is available thanks to the high-res primary, as well as Nightscape and Chroma boost modes.  Realme 5 Pro review Another thing the Realme 5 Pro impresses with is the large battery and the presence of 20W VOOC charging via the USB-C port.  And last, but of huge importance, is the fact that the Realme 5 Pro is the company's first-ever splash-resistant phone.  Realme 5 Pro specs Body: Gorilla Glass 3+ front, polycarbonate back, splash-proof Screen: 6.3-inch IPS LCD, 19:9, 1080p+, 409ppi Rear camera: Primary 48MP Quad Bayer 1/2&quot; sensor, f/1.8 lens; 119Â° ultra wide-angle 8MP camera; 2MP macro camera; 2MP depth sensor; LED flash; 2160p@30fps video recording, EIS Front camera: 16MP Quad Bayer sensor, f/2.0 lens; EIS Chipset: Snapdragon 712: octa-core CPU (2x2.2 GHz Kryo 360 Gold & 6x1.7 GHz Kryo 360 Silver), Adreno 616 GPU Memory: 4/64GB, 6/64GB or 8/128GB; UFS 2.1 storage; dedicated microSD slot for up to 256GB expansion OS: Android 9.0; Color OS 6.0 on top Battery: 4,035mAh, 20W VOOC 3.0 charging Connectivity: Dual SIM (4G), Bluetooth 5.0, Wi-Fi a/b/g/n, USB-C Colors: Crystal Green, Crystal Blue Misc: Rear-mounted fingerprint reader Realme 5 Pro isn't a significant update over the Realme 3 Pro as far as screen and performance are concerned. In fact - those stay the same. But the camera seems light years ahead and may as well make people that bought the Realme 3 jump to 5 in no time. How things will turn out? Let's find out!  Unboxing the Realme 5 Pro The Realme 5 Pro comes packed into a rather bulky paper box but it's full of goodies. The maker ships the phone with the 20W VOOC charger and the proprietary USB-C cable needed for the VOOC to work properly.  Realme 5 Pro review The bundle also contains a semi-transparent gray silicone case that will help keep the beauty of the Realme 5 Pro unspoiled for quite a while.  NEXT PAGE » 2. Design and 360-degree view 1. Introduction, specs, retail package Reviews  Realme 5 Pro review COMMENTS (93) USER REVIEWS 5 PRO  REALME 5 PRO REVIEW - READER COMMENTS C Colrahul y0K24 Feb 2020 It doesn't get hot even after playing call of duty.  Reply U Umar f}m09 Feb 2020 Are you sure? What protector are you using now?  Reply D DC YQP08 Feb 2020 Have been using this phone over a week. Good phone. Battery lasts over a day with lot of you-tube videos, FB, phone calls and surfing. Call clarity is good. Internet speed is also good -no lag. No heating issues. Overall quite content with the phone....  Reply READ ALL COMMENTSPOST YOUR COMMENTTotal reader comments: 93  PHONE FINDER SAMSUNG APPLE HUAWEI NOKIA SONY LG HTC MOTOROLA LENOVO XIAOMI GOOGLE HONOR OPPO REALME ONEPLUS VIVO MEIZU BLACKBERRY ASUS ALCATEL ZTE MICROSOFT VODAFONE ENERGIZER CAT SHARP MICROMAX INFINIX ULEFONE TECNO BLU ACER WIKO PANASONIC VERYKOOL PLUM  ALL BRANDS RUMOR MILL  RELATED ARTICLES  Realme X50 Pro 5G to arrive in China on March 12  Realme 6 Pro's promo video features Salman Khan, is all about the cameras and display  Realme 6 and Realme 6 Pro official: 64MP quad cameras, It might have been just over a year, but we are glad Realme has found its MO - catchy designs, breezy performance, and good camera skillset. And it's been delivering those on unbelievably low prices ever since. The Realme 5 Pro doesn't lose focus on what's important either - there is the signature dazzling looks, the upper-tier Snapdragon 712 chip, and company's first quad-camera setup.Indeed, Realme has jumped from dual- straight to quad-camera arrangements. And the Realme 5 Pro setup is rather impressive with a 48MP primary, an 8MP ultrawide, a 2MP macro, and 2MP portrait snappers. Advanced 2x digital zoom is available thanks to the high-res primary, as well as Nightscape and Chroma boost modes.Another thing the Realme 5 Pro impresses with is the large battery and the presence of 20W VOOC charging via the USB-C port.  And last, but of huge importance, is the fact that the Realme 5 Pro is the company's first-ever splash-resistant phone.
    <string name="teks">values</string>
</resources>